Fresh steamed buns, piping hot!
Two, please. Coming right up.
Here you are.
Why are there so many imperial guards on
the street?
You haven't heard?
The Weisu delegation enters the capital
today.
The number of patrols in the city
has doubled these past two days.
Weisu?
They've been quiet for over ten years.
I heard the Noble Consort wanted to see
her family.
The visit was arranged long ago.
Who knew...
The delegation is here!
They've already reached the city gate.
They're here! Come on!
Let's go have a look!
So these are the Weisu people.
They're so tall.
Aside from being taller and stronger,
Otherwise, they look much like us.
Just a bunch of barbarians.
What's there to see?
If Dingyuan hadn't led the Yulin cavalry
north and broken through Weisu,
those barbarians would still be making
trouble.
Under the emperor's nose? Do you want to
die?
Look!
Who's that leading them on horseback?
He's quite handsome.
I heard they have a general named Helian
Zhao.
A young hero.
He's won many battles for Weisu these past
two years.
Could that be him?
General, word has come from the palace.
The delegation will enter the palace
today.
They will rest first.
Tomorrow at dusk, the palace will host a
banquet.
All right. I understand.
Move on.
Outrageous.
The streets are crawling with imperial
guards today.
With the Noble Consort backing them,
so they strut about Great Chu with such
fanfare.
Enough.
For now, we must summon Prince Yu back
soon.
I'll have someone see to it.
How dare you!
This place is...
This is where rebels gather to plot
treason.
Chief.
Take these three rebels back.
Yes.
What rebels?
Let go!
Chu Mingke!
On what grounds are you arresting us?
On the grounds that His Majesty granted me
the right to execute first and report
later.
Bah! A dog borrowing its master's power.
Nothing but a castrated cur.
For every insult, I slap you once.
Chu Mingke, how dare you!
Lord Chen is a servant of Great Chu.
How dare you strike him?
Bah! Eunuch dog!
Insult me again.
Eunuch dogs are ruining the state. I swear
I will...
Take him away.
His Majesty will not let you get away with
this!
The eunuch faction is ruining the state!
Your Excellency.
My lord, you honor me too much.
The delegation enters the capital today.
May I ask, Your Excellency,
why you are here?
There is something I cannot understand
either.
The city is filled with imperial guards
today.
How could rebels be plotting here?
I do not care why these three gathered
here.
But if you dare make trouble under my nose
again,
I will cut off your head
and hang it before Lingji Palace as a
lantern.
Move.
Farewell, Your Excellency.
Who came with the delegation?
Mostly tribal nobles.
And a young general named Helian Zhao.
Central Plains wine has no kick.
It goes down soft and limp.
The land and water are different.
So customs and food are different too.
If you want something strong and pure,
the grasslands will have plenty when you
return.
This Shunjing...
From flowers to people,
everything is delicate as paper.
If this were Weisu,
one gust of wind would knock them over.
Indeed.
Shunjing's winter plums can't bear prairie
winds.
Your Excellency, please hurry over.
His Majesty is still waiting for you
inside.
Understood.
Your Majesty, I'm late.
It seems Fengtian Hall is far too large.
You lost your way just walking through it.
Mingke.
Yes.
My lord, you are...
You are quite unreasonable, my lord.
Attacking without a word.
Your strikes are merciless, my lord.
What a waste of those tender eyes.
Too much chatter.
My lord,
you smell of blood.
You are about to lose.
Why not say something sweet?
Then I might go easy on you.
Have you ever heard the saying,
Pride comes before defeat?
I don't need anyone to go easy on me to
win.
You lost.
Your subject, Chu Mingke, kneels before
Your Majesty.
The arrowhead is sharp.
It may wound Your Majesty.
Let me remove it.
You may leave.
Yes.
Rise.
You were right.
This blade is indeed sharp.
Hold this.
Your Majesty, it is time for your elixir.
A report from Shanxi says Duan Yunping is
gravely ill.
His time is near.
General Duan has governed Shanxi for
decades.
He is a true hero.
Even the greatest heroes grow old.
As for Helian Zhao...
He rose to fame at a young age.
His edge is too exposed.
He is barely nineteen now.
He is indeed a born commander.
Indeed.
A pity he was born in Weisu.
Those not of our kind
are bound to have different hearts.
Enough.
These are troubled times.
Use your own judgment in all things.
Yes.
Your Excellency, my lord!
You've finally come!
Your Excellency!
Please go see Her Highness at once!
What happened to Her Highness?
I don't know.
She has raged since returning from the
banquet.
No one can talk her down.
She has smashed many things.
Get out!
All you ungrateful wretches, get out!
Your Highness!
Please calm down, Your Highness.
If Your Highness is angry,
beat me to death if you must.
Just do not harm your own body.
Your jade hands are soft and beautiful.
What if you hurt them?
Does it hurt?
No.
Please don't be angry anymore, Your
Highness.
Get down there and kneel properly.
Who told you to beat him?
You disobeyed me.
You always win.
You Central Plains people always win.
Isn't that enough?
You've grown up.
Your wings have hardened.
Now you want to fly off on your own.
Is that it? Insolent thing!
Have you forgotten what you once promised
me?
Mingke...
Do not blame me.
Your Highness, I haven't forgotten.
I will never forget.
It was my fault.
Please do not make yourself ill with
anger.
In this palace, you are the only one who
cares for me.
Everyone else only upsets me.
Who has upset Your Highness?
Consort Chen, of course.
Consort Chen found some tramp to seduce
His Majesty.
The pregnant palace maid in the plum
garden.
Go. Kill her.
Yes.
Doing wicked deeds this late, my lord...
aren't you afraid wronged ghosts will come
for you?
A wronged ghost?
Better that than a mangy cur who will not
let go.
So you actually remember me, my lord.
I thought you were a heartless man
and had long forgotten me.
Could it be that you miss me
as fiercely as I miss you?
I miss the day you die.
Then you can only keep longing for it.
I am an honored guest of the delegation.
If I also become a drowned corpse in the
pond,
how would your country explain it?
My lord.
You cannot kill me.
Do you know what living worse than death
means?
Such strength, my lord.
So passionate the moment we meet.
I am almost flattered.
So cold to me?
After all, I fell for you at first sight,
and fell deeper at second sight.
Move.
Who's there?